[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Robert Altman films was not released in 1970s?", "correct_answer": "Popeye", "incorrect_answers": ["Nashville", "3 Women", "M*A*S*H"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This villain from a 1964 Bond movie ranks #49 on AFIs list of the 50 top villains.", "correct_answer": "Auric Goldfinger", "incorrect_answers": ["Dr. No", "Blofield", "The Russians"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Soon after WWII, this Opel model was transferred to the Soviet Union and formed the basis for the Soviet car Moskvitch 400/420.", "correct_answer": "Kadett", "incorrect_answers": ["Arena", "Vectra", "Rekord"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To what continent is the rose species commonly known as Gallic Rose native?", "correct_answer": "Europe", "incorrect_answers": ["North America", "Asia", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who killed the Nemean Lion, one of the most vicious monsters in Greek mythology?", "correct_answer": "Heracles", "incorrect_answers": ["Zeus", "Cronus", "King Eurystheus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ochlophobia is the fear of being shut in.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the scene in The African Queen where Charlie was pulling The Queen through the overgrowth, Huston used real leeches in the water without telling Bogart, so his revulsion would be real.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ketchikan, Alaska holds what distinction?", "correct_answer": "the highest zip code for an American city", "incorrect_answers": ["the highest ratio of males to females of any American city", "the highest amount of snow fall in an American city", "the highest number of days of precipitation for any American city"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where do Alan Stanwyks parents live in the comedy film Fletch?", "correct_answer": "Provo, Utah", "incorrect_answers": ["Los Angeles, California", "Boise, Idaho", "Austin, Texas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed and starred in the comedy movie The Ladies Man?", "correct_answer": "Jerry Lewis", "incorrect_answers": ["Ben Stiller", "John Witherspoon", "Rob Schneider"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The church of Hagia Irene, a Byzantine church, was converted into a mosque by Sultan Mehmed the Conquerer.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the possible origins of the popular expression rule of thumb  is believed to be connected to the process of brewing beer.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]